quiz = {
    1: {'question':'You may drive off the paved roadway to pass another vehicle:', 'answers':['If the shoulder is wide enough to accommodate your vehicle.',
'If the vehicle ahead of you is turning left.',
'Under no circumstances.'
], 'correct':2},
    2: {'question':'When approaching a railroad crossing with no warning device, the speed limit is:', 'answers':['15 mph.','20 mph.','25 mph.'
], 'correct':0},
    3: {'question':' Parallel parking is when the:', 'answers':['Front wheels are turned toward the street.','Vehicle is in line with other parked vehicles.',
'Rear wheels are touching the curb.'
], 'correct':1},
    4: {'question':'When you are merging onto the freeway, you should be driving:', 'answers':['At or near the same speed as the traffic on the freeway.',
'5 to 10 MPH slower than the traffic on the freeway.', 'The posted speed limit for traffic on the freeway.'
], 'correct':0},
    5: {'question':'Dim your high-beam headlights to low-beams within ______ feet when a vehicle is coming towards you.', 'answers':['200','300',
'500'
], 'correct':2},
    6: {'question':'A blue curb means:', 'answers':['Parking for mail delivery only.','Parking for disabled persons with a special placard or license plate.',
'Parking for disabled persons.'
], 'correct':1},
    7: {'question':'There is a school bus ahead of you in your lane with flashing yellow lights. You should:', 'answers':['Stop, then proceed when you think all the children have exited the bus.',
'Slow to 25 MPH and pass cautiously.','Slow down and prepare to stop.'
], 'correct':2},
    8: {'question':'California Basic Speed Law says:','answers':['You should never drive faster than posted speed limits.',
'You should never drive faster than is safe for current conditions.','The maximum speed limit in California is 70 mph on certain freeways.'
], 'correct':1},
    9: {'question':'You just sold your vehicle. You must notify ______ within 5 days.', 'answers':['CHP',
'DMV','Your insurance provider'
], 'correct':1},
    10: {'question':' Looking down the road to where your vehicle will be in about 10 seconds helps you to ______________.', 'answers':['Enjoy the scenery',
'Avoid last minute moves','See hazards inside your car'
], 'correct':1},
}